Kathryn E. Perry

113 Spring Fawn, Cibolo, Texas 78108 keperry30@icloud.com | 210-556-5093

Human Resource Management

Proven leadership skills combined with an exceptional ability to manage multiple large-scale projects, tasks and priorities effectively and in a timely manner. Extensive formal training and 20+ years of experience at all levels of leadership. Swiftly comprehends the "big picture" and executes the boldest of organizational visions. Superior communicator, effective at all organizational levels. Core competencies include:

- Mentoring and Training
- Sets Performance Standards
- Guides Process Improvement
- Superb Presentation Skills
- Analytical Problem Solver
- Highly Detail Oriented
- Quality Assurance Evaluator
- Customer Service
- Excellent People Skills

Professional Experience

Project Coordination and Personnel Management

Employs strict attention to detail with a stute planning skills to optimize organizational budgets, meet or exceed employee scheduling requirements and maximize personnel availability. Career highlighted by success and constant achievement.

- Worked hand in hand with leadership to ensure organizational programs were maintained and running smoothly
- Responsible for automated data processing equipment accounts, ensured property was 100 percent accounted for
- Oversaw government purchasing programs, provided continuous supprt throughout the organization
- Managed organizational budgets, coordinated the purchase and replacement of warehouse stock levels

Analysis and Training

Consistently implements keen analytical abilities and a proven team-based work dynamic with a systemsoriented approach to facilitate efficient and effective solutions. A critical thinker open to alternative views to optimize decision-making.

- Conducted inspections on all aspects of materiel management functions, provided written reports and briefed leadership on the findings
- Provided detailed research of regulations and policies thereby ensuring organizational procedures and operating instructions followed as required
- Communicated with others throughout the company in order to develop and implement solutions to allow for proper procedures when needed

Leadership and Supervision

A superior leader with demonstrated performance in high-pressure environments. Improved organizational performance through hands-on training and a leadership approach that emphasized decision-making through active listening.

- Supervised shops ranging from 4 to 49 personnel
- Handpicked as the dedicated focal point for all readiness, health, morale, welfare and quality-of-life issues within the organization
- Performs performance reviews on 49 personnel to aid in career advancement and production improvement

Employment

U.S. Air Force, Various Duty Stations 1995 - 2017

Section Chief, Flight Service Center 2016–2017

Non-Commissioned Officer in Charge (NCOIC), Customer Support 2015–2016

Non-Commissioned Officer in Charge (NCOIC), Inventory Management 2012–2015

Non-Commissioned Officer in Charge (NCOIC), Maintenance Support 2010–2012

Assistant First Sergeant 2009–2010

Non-Commissioned Officer in Charge (NCOIC), Logistical Support 2008–2009

Assistant Non-Commissioned Officer in Charge (NCOIC), Hazardous Materiels Pharmacy 2007–2008

Non-Commissioned Officer in Charge (NCOIC), Joint Services Recreational Facility 2006–2007

Materiel Control Technician 2003-2006

Supply Technician 1995–2003

Education and Training

Texas State University, San Marcos, TX

Bachelor Degree awarded 12/2022 Major: Computer Information Systems Concentration: Business Analytics

GPA: 4.0

Texas State University, San Marcos, TX

Bachelor Degree awarded 12/2020 Major: Appplied Mathematics Minor: Business Administration

GPA: 3.8

Honors: Summa Cum Laude

Community College of the Air Force, Maxwell, AL

Associate Degree awarded 12/2007

Major: Logistics

GPA: 3.5

Internships

Company: USAA

Section: Information Technology Job Title: Data Engineer Intern Dates: 1 July - 12 August 2022

Professional Military Education

Senior Non-Commissioned Officer Academy (Correspondence) – 09/2013 Non-Commissioned Officer Academy (In Residence) – 07/2009 First Sergeant Additional Duty Training (In Residence) – 06/2008 Intermediate Materiel Management Training (In Residence) – 08/2002 Airman Leadership School (In Residence) – 06/2001 Materiel Management Training (In Residence) – 03/1996

Relevant Coursework and Certifications

Fundamentals of Logistics, Air Force Institute of Technology Collaborative Inventory Planning, Air Force Institute of Technology Green Belt Training, Air Force Continuous Process Improvemeny Logistics Readiness Quality Assurance Evaluator Course Wing Inspection Team Course Government Purchase Card

Computer Skills

MS Office Suite (Word, PowerPoint, Excel, Access) Adobe Creative Suite CS6 LATEX

Programming

C++

С#

MATLAB

R

HTML

CSS

Visual Basic

Python